[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This leading American brand of denim jeans, introduced in the mid-1940s, was originally developed for rodeo use.", "correct_answer": "Wrangler", "incorrect_answers": ["Levis", "Gap", "Armani"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take Mars to complete one revolution around the sun?", "correct_answer": "687 days", "incorrect_answers": ["225 days", "525 days", "456 days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Regardless of its size, approximately this much of an iceberg is visible above the waterline.", "correct_answer": "1/9", "incorrect_answers": ["3/4", "1/3", "1/25"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What class of horse breed does the Clydesdale horse belong to?", "correct_answer": "Draft Horse", "incorrect_answers": ["Carriage Horse", "Farm Horse", "Saddle Horse"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "She was often called The female Ed Wood.", "correct_answer": "Doris Wishman", "incorrect_answers": ["Nora Ephron", "Susan Seidelman", "Nikki Leder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When was the United Nations founded?", "correct_answer": "1945", "incorrect_answers": ["1947", "1948", "1946"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term rigor mortis means this.", "correct_answer": "Stiffness of death", "incorrect_answers": ["Swollen corpse", "Blue corpse", "Blue death"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The capital of Mongolia is this city.", "correct_answer": "Ulaanbaatar", "incorrect_answers": ["Davao", "Islamabad", "Quezon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ammonites became extinct at the end of what geological period?", "correct_answer": "Cretaceous", "incorrect_answers": ["Jurassic", "Triassic", "Permian"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1985 movie Fletch, Fletch charges several meals to whose credit card?", "correct_answer": "Mr. Underhills", "incorrect_answers": ["Mr. Stanwyks", "Mr. Dolans", "Mr. Karlins"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How does the lightsaber battle between Darth Vader and Ben Kenobi end in Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope?", "correct_answer": "Darth Vader defeats Ben Kenobi.", "incorrect_answers": ["Ben Kenobi retreats.", "Darth Vader retreats.", "Ben Kenobi defeats Darth Vader."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which movie is Bernardo Bertoluccis directorial debut?", "correct_answer": "La commare secca (The Grim Reaper)", "incorrect_answers": ["La Luna", "Il Canale", "Partner"]}]